<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>research on Dressing Up Data</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in research on Dressing Up Data</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Post</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/new-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/new-project/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Long time no see! Friends, it’s been a very busy semester and holiday season. But, I want to share some updates before the winter semester starts next week!
New Digital Exhibit I took two wonderful history classes this semester. Taking Technology in US History was an absolute highlight for me; the course started out solidly in my 18th and 19th century comfort zone, covering railroads, mills, and agriculture, but by the second half we were talking about modern technology that I regularly use but hadn’t thought about critically.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Duties as Assigned: Recapping My Nancy Drew Summer</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/2022-06-27-my-nancy-drew-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/2022-06-27-my-nancy-drew-summer/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            It’s up to you as Nancy Drew… Did you know that between 1998 and 2015, the video game company HER Interactive released 32 Nancy Drew PC point-and-click adventure games? If you’ve spent any time with me in real life, then you definitely know about them, since I love them and talk about them constantly. I very regularly start a sentence with “Well, there’s this one Nancy Drew game where…”
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Shiny or Not to Shiny</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/2022-06-14-to-shiny-or-not-to-shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/2022-06-14-to-shiny-or-not-to-shiny/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            That is the question… Shiny is one of my favorite R packages.
For those who aren’t R enthusiasts (or those who are but haven’t yet been introduced to Shiny), Shiny is an R package that allows you to create interactive applications. With a single script, you can super easily create a UI and server that will take user input and generate graphs, tables, text, and even maps.
So far, I’ve mostly used Shiny to level up my leaflet game.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week One at Rufus Porter</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/rpm-week-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/rpm-week-one/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Figure 1: Mural from the Francis Howe House, painted by Rufus Porter and Stephen Twombly Porter in 1838. Photo by David Bohl via the University of Maine.  Happy summer! This week I started my summer internship at the Rufus Porter Museum of Art and Ingenuity in Bridgton, Maine. The RPM is a very small museum - I’m one of three employees at the moment - so I really get to see all the different sides of running a museum.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
